<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">EndGame</string>
    <string name="title_activity_init">InitActivity</string>
    <string name="game_name">ENDGAME</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_host">HostActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_join">JoinActivity</string>
    <string name="dialogMsgButtonText">OK</string>
    <string name="title_activity_instructions">InstructionsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game">GameActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dialog">DialogActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="hosting_title">Hosting...</string>
    <string name="hosting_breadtext">Your Gamecode:</string>
    <string name="Back">Back</string>
    <string name="Init_button_host">Host A Game</string>
    <string name="init_button_join">Join A Game</string>
    <string name="init_button_instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="joining_title">Joining...</string>
    <string name="joining_breadtext">Enter Code Here</string>
    <string name="joining_button_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="instruction_string">Instructions: \n When hosting a game you are given a string of characters, these are connected to a newly created game on our Server. \n Joining a server requires you to enter another persons gamecode and submitting it. \n Now you should already be playing the game</string>
    //dialog    <string name="introAxis">Agent Schwartz!\nWir haben ein mission for you!\nEin English agent has been zighted in Schweiz.\nEin technology-institüt haben eine Gruppe Zcientists.\nDu musste Extrakte them\nViel Glögg\n</string>
    <string name="introAllies">Smith! .. Smith! .. Do you copy?\nGood.\nWe got a new one for ya, this time it\'s in Switzerland!\nTheres a group of scientists fortified in a bunker, we need you to extract them ASAP.\nBecareful though, before locking themself in they activated the landmines around the facility.\nTake care Laddie. </string>
    <string name="winAxis">Sehr Gut!\nMit der Zcientists in unsere hands, die next step is reicht in front of uz.\nWir haben ein paar Optionen:\n\nA. Ein superserum dat will make unsere soldaten super stärk.\n\nB. Ein Atomspränghovet to blöw up unsere enemiez.\n\nC. Ein neue Missil-prototypen, dat we mit unsere Zcientist massen-produceren kann.\n\nDie valg is deine.\n </string>
    <string name="winAllies">Good job Smith, i knew we could count on ya.\nAlright with the intel we\'ve gotten from the scientist, we already have the next steps planned.\nWe\'ve got a couple options, we\'ll let you decide where ya wanna go:\n\nA. The scientist knew about a secret super serum project.\n\nB. We got some intel on a series of nuclear warheads that we\'d like you to look at.\n\nC. A new missile prototype has been discovered. Go get it for us.</string>
    <string name="loseAxis">NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN\nDAS WAR EIN BEFEHL!\nSchwarts ich bin really skuffet in dich\nach, oh wëll\nWir must warten und see was die English do next.\n </string>
    <string name="loseAllies">Well shit.\nAlright Smith, we\'ll get them on the next one.\nRight now we\'ll keep a lookout for their next move.\nWe will have you on standby till then. \nBe ready when we next contact you.\nOut....\n </string>
    <string name="introductionAllies">You are a secret agent working under the name of "Smith", hired by the British covert ops.\n \n In a world troubled by war you are sent on secret missions, ususally requiring you to extract intel or important items, in an attempt to tip the scales in favor of Britain.\n \n You already know that Nazi Germany have a similarly working unit as the British covert ops, they will most likely try to hinder you and steal the objects of value under your nose.</string>
    <string name="introductionAxis">You are a secret agent working under the name of "Schwartz", hired by the Schutzstaffel, the secret nazi police.\n \n In a world troubled by war you are sent on secret missions, ususally requiring you to extract intel or important items, in an attempt to tip the scales in favor of Germany.\n \n You already know that the British army have a similarly covert ops unit, they will most likely try to hinder you and steal the objects of value under your nose.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_introduction">IntroductionActivity</string>

</resources>
